Matt: This was a slow process.
It would have started about '96 when I
was at uni and some friends suggested it.
It started to get suggested a
bit more frequently around 2000.
And I remember asking mental health
professionals during periods of depression
and anxiety about it as far back as 2005.
But, yeah, I didn't really seriously
start approaching mental health
professionals about it until about 2015.
Diagnosis came through 20...
autumn of 2016.
This was quite a lengthy process
because I went to my GP, I think early
2015 and was initially turned away.
But went back and went home and thought
about it some more and gathered some
more evidence, both from online tests
and from what friends had told me and
about issues that I experienced in work
and socialising in general, went back
to the GP  and said to them, "look,
here's, here's some more evidence.
I know you, you say that you
don't want to put a label on it.
You say that it's likely to be expensive.
You say that I'm going to have to go out
of area, but I'm, I'm not going away.
I'm going to keep going back
until I get this referral".
And so they offered me the referral.
I'm in Manchester, central area.
I think there are two nearby one
is - two two adult autism referral
services - one is in Trafford and
one is, I don't know, Bolton, Oldham.
It's somewhere elsewhere
outside of the city.
And they all have long waiting lists.
So I was eventually put on
the waiting list for Trafford.
And then there was I think,
I think it's three stages.
There was certainly two or three
interviews as part of that process.
And then they went off and met
with their team and eventually
came up with the diagnosis for me.